<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on the closing box</title>
    <link>https://theclosingbox.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on the closing box</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theclosingbox.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>macpro build - day 2</title>
      <link>https://theclosingbox.com/posts/mac-pro-buildlog-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theclosingbox.com/posts/mac-pro-buildlog-04/</guid>
      <description>Day two is dedicated to some early annoyance fixes, and some temperature and performance measurements of the NVMe storage.
a tiny fan With a little more burn in time in a quiet room, I noticed a change in the sound profile of the Mac Pro. The addition of the Syba I/O card had added in a high-pitched, whiny fan noise. This didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to ramp up and down with temperatures on the M.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>macpro build - day 1</title>
      <link>https://theclosingbox.com/posts/mac-pro-buildlog-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theclosingbox.com/posts/mac-pro-buildlog-03/</guid>
      <description>the machine It begins! First, we&amp;rsquo;ll verify our day 0 assumptions, and examine the machine itself.
  A first peek inside
  All told, it&amp;rsquo;s cosmetically fine. I&amp;rsquo;d love a more pristine chassis (this guy has definitely been bounced off some rough corners), but it was relatively clean on the inside. I blew the machine out with compressed air and wiped down all of touchable surfaces before really cracking in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>macpro build - day 0</title>
      <link>https://theclosingbox.com/posts/mac-pro-buildlog-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theclosingbox.com/posts/mac-pro-buildlog-02/</guid>
      <description>Now that we now what we&amp;rsquo;re going to try to do here and why, let&amp;rsquo;s formulate some kind of plan for this project.
the plan I&amp;rsquo;m going to start with the lowest spec 2 processor tray. I might have been able to find a better deal on a single processor machine and then source a dual proc CPU tray, but from a cursory search of ebay and craigslist, that might take a while, and I&amp;rsquo;m a little concerned about extra shipping cycles and part availability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>macpro build - what and why</title>
      <link>https://theclosingbox.com/posts/mac-pro-buildlog-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theclosingbox.com/posts/mac-pro-buildlog-01/</guid>
      <description>In March of 2020, I went looking for a project. I was looking for something that I could focus some extra time and energy on (that wasn&amp;rsquo;t just frantically refreshing news sites). I was working from home full time for the first time in my life, a change which necessitated some alterations to my workspace. Graduate school was finished, so I could afford some instability on my personal machine, and the 5k iMac that had served as the anchor of my home computing life was now in the way (I couldn&amp;rsquo;t use it for work, so it ended up awkwardly shunted aside most days, and moving it back into place every night was just annoying enough to be untenable.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>